《迷失》前情回顾
Previously on "lost"...
这是你的女儿
This is your daughter.
她叫Clementine
Her name's clementine.
-这些项链是假的  -我要最后那条
-Those are fake necklaces. -I'll take the one on the end.
-为什么帮我  -同是女人
-Why'd you help me? -just one girl
理应出手相助
Watching another girl's back, I guess.
我有个女儿在Albuquerque
I have a daughter in Albuquerque.
-为什么告诉我  -按我说的做  雀斑女
-Why are you telling me this? -just do it, freckles.
应该说他是我的孩子
I think we should say he's mine.
还有别的解决方式
There's other ways to do this.
我们已经失去了那么多人
After everyone we've lost,
不能再失去他了
I can't lose him, too.
我的客户坚持要
My client insists that we...
私下交接监护权
Handle the exchange of custody quietly.
你会失去这个男孩
You are going to lose the boy.
那是Claire的妈妈
That's claire's mother.
Kate和我做的一切  都是为了Aaron
Everything that kate and I have done, it was for aaron.
Aaron是谁
Who's... aaron?
我是Ben
I'm ben.
见到你很高兴  Ben
It's nice to meet you, ben.
如果我放你出来
If I let you out....
你能带我去找你的人吗
Will you take me with you to your people?
这就是我的任务
That's why I'm here.
Jin  你在这做什么
Jin? what are you doing here
Jin  你在听吗
Hello, jin? are you there?
能听到吗  Jin
Jin?! can you hear me?
我在听
Hello?
Jin  是我  Phil
Jin? it's...it's phil, man.
你去哪里了  敌人跑了
Where have you been? the hostile escaped.
我们在东区搜查
We're searching the east grid.
他往北去了
He's headed north.
你怎么知道
How the hell do you know that?
他袭击了我
Because he attacked me.
什么  你在哪里
What? where are you?
Jin  你还在吗
Jin?! you still there?
Jin  Jin
Jin?  Jin!
帮帮我
Please help.
所有人  听好  放在这边
Okay, everybody, listen up. put it over there.
我们不知道是否还会遭袭
We don't know yet if another attack is coming.
所有人都要准备好
So everybody needs to be ready
做好安全工作  好吗
For your security assignments, okay?
和队长保持联系
Make sure you're in contact with your team leaders.
Lafleur已经派出了搜捕队
Lafleur's got search parties out,
但敌人侥幸逃脱了
But the hostile's got a good jump on us.
可以确定他利用了这堆火
We're pretty sure he used this fire as a diversion
来逃脱
In order to escape.
他在说Sayid吗
Uh... is he talking about sayid?
如果被锁着  他怎么可能点火呢
If he was locked up, how could he start the fire?
你是谁
Who are you?
Jack Shephard  我是新来的
Jack shephard. I'm... I'm new.
能点起火是因为有人帮了他
Well, jack, the way he started the fire is he had help, okay?
有人把车点着了
somebody torched that van,
还把他从牢房里放了出来
And then that somebody let him out of his cell.
由于监控器没发现有敌人
And since the security cameras didn'tick up any hostiles
那个帮手就是我们中的一个
Crossing the perimeter, that means it was one of us.
Baxter  我要清理报告  越快越好
Baxter, I want a full report on cleanup a.s.a.p.
明白  Horace
You got it, horace.
你
Hey, you.
就说你呢
Yeah, you.
-你负责车库的吧  -是的
-You're in the motor pool, right? -uh, yeah.
能帮我转一下绞轮吗
Do you mind running that winch for me?
根本不知道我在说什么吗
You have no idea what I'm talking about, do you?
别担心  只要撬这个杠杆
Okay, no worries. just throw this lever.
我说停的时候  你就拽起来
When I tell you to stop... just pull it up.
明白吗  很简单  我说好之前先别动
All right. see? simple. don't do it till I'm ready.
好的  开始转吧
Okay. all right, crank her up.
你刚来就被塞到车库了吗
So they just stuck you in the motor pool when you got here?
差不多吧
yeah, pretty much.
我也是  等一下  拉住
Yeah, same thing happened to me. wait, hold.
停在那里  很好  就这样
Hold it there. that's good right there. that's good.
要是早知道会来做油腻的工人
I guess they couldn't sucker anybody into getting on that sub
没人会被哄上那艘潜艇的
If they told us we were gonna be grease monkeys and janitors.
总要慢慢开始嘛
Well, you gotta start somewhere, right?
没错  你叫什么
Yeah. what's your name?
我是Kate
I'm kate.
欢迎入伙  Kate
Welcome aboard, kate.
我是Roger  Roger Linus
I'm roger. roger linus.
很高兴认识你  Roger
It's nice to meet you, roger.
那是我的孩子
That's my kid.
我的孩子
That's my kid!
小帅哥
Hi, handsome.
睡得好吗
Did you have a good sleep?
乖孩子
Yeah, that's my boy.
天呐
Oh, my god!
你好  Cassidy
Hi, cassidy.
老天  我在新闻上看到你了
Oh, my god! I saw you on the news!
我告诉所有朋友  我认识那女人
I told all my friends, "i know that woman!"
-你好  -这是Aaron
-Hi! -this is aaron.
你好呀  Aaron
Hi, aaron.
说你好
Say hi.
你从坠机中幸存了下来
You survived a plane crash.
太惊人了  没想到我还能见到你
It's amazing. I never thought I'd see you again.
你在这做什么
What are you doing here?
Sawyer让我来的
Sawyer sent me.
Sawyer 那个混蛋还活着吗
Sawyer. So that son of a bitch is still alive?
我离开的时候还活着
He was when I left.
他让你来
And he asked you to come here
给我一信封的钱吗
And give me an envelope full of money?
他告诉我怎么找到你
Well, he...he told me where to find you, and...
说要好好照顾Clementine
Said to take care of clementine...
她正在摇篮里睡着呢
Well, she's asleep in her crib right now.
要我把她叫醒吗
Want me to wake her up?
我不该过来打扰
I, uh, shouldn't have bothered you.
我本应寄过来的  那样更好些
I could've sent it, and I probably should have.
为什么告诉我这些
Why did you tell me all this?
为什么相信我
Why'd you trust me?
因为我觉得他的女儿  有权知道
Because I thought your daughter had a right to know
他爸爸很想她
That her father cared.
他为什么不和你们一起回来
Why didn't he come back with the rest of you?
我们坐的飞机没油了
The helicopter that we were on was running out of gas,
他跳机了
So he jumped
这样我们才能坚持到船上
So that we could make it to the boat.
真是懦夫
What a coward.
他只是想做正确的事
He was trying to do the right thing.
他只是想离开你
He was trying to get away from you.
我告诉他  他有个女儿
I told him he had a daughter.
他都不敢抬手给她打个电话
He never so much as lifted a finger to try to call her.
而现在  我得把他当成英雄
So now I'm supposed to think he's a hero
只因为他让你过来帮我们
Because he told you to come here and help us?
这钱都不是他的吧
Hell, I bet this money's not even his, is it?
坠机后我们收到一笔抚恤金
They gave us a settlement after the crash,
-我用不了这么多  -不用解释  Kate
-And I didn't need it all -you don't have to explain it, kate.
你的表情和我被他甩了时一样
You got the same look on your face I did when he ditched me.
对你我只有同情
All I have for you is sympathy.
是他的吗
Is it his?
什么
What?
你的儿子
Your son.
是Sawyer的吗
Is it Sawyer's?
不是
No.
不  我...
No, I was...
在认识他之前就怀孕了
Pregnant before I met him.
那不是你的孩子  对吗
That's not your baby, is it?
Kate  你刚刚告诉我你和你的朋友们
Kate, you just told me that you and your friends
向全世界编造了一个故事
Cooked a story for the whole world
来隐瞒在小岛上发生的事情
About what happened on that island.
因此你怎么会对我说真话
So you tell me the truth about that?
关于他  你为什么要对我撒谎
Why are you lying to me about him?
因为我不得不这么做
Because I have to.
发生了什么事
What happened?
你在这里做什么
What the hell are you doing here?
是Ben  被枪击的孩子是Ben
That was Ben. that kid who was shot was Ben.
是不是Sayid干的  他打了那孩子一枪
Was it Sayid? did he shoot him?
这才是你需要做的  Kate
here's what you need to do, Kate
闭上你的嘴不要再问任何问题
Keep your mouth shut and stop asking questions.
因为在你身上花功夫
'cause putting any attention on yourself is
是我现在最不想做的事情  快点走
The last thing I need right now. now scram.
我不想让你在这里
I don't want you around here.
我只想知道发生了什么
I just wanna know what's going on.
Lafleur  怎么...
Lafleur. what...
怎么  她在这里干什么
What, uh... what's she doing here?
-这是...  -我是Kate
-This is, uh... -I'm Kate.
她是新来的  在车辆调配厂
she's new over at the motor pool.
我只是想看看她有没有看到任何可疑的事情
I was seeing if she saw anything suspicious,
她没发现什么  那么你可以走了  谢谢
But she didn't so... you can run along, Thanks.
你有没有查看过敌人的牢房
Have you checked out the hostile's cell yet?
我正忙着
I was a little busy
不让这个小镇被烧光  Horace
Trying to keep the town from burnin' down, Horace.
那么好吧  我们现在去
Okay. well, then let's do it.
他没有破坏门  是有人放他出去的
He didn't break out. somebody let him out.
那是管理员的钥匙
These are janitor's keys.
我们只有三个管理员
We've only got three janitors.
是Roger  Willie  还有那个新人  我才见过他
There's Roger, Willie and, uh, that new guy. I just met him.
他名叫Jack  我刚把他从潜艇里带出来
His name's Jack. yeah. I just brought him in from the sub.
我去跟他谈谈  Miles  跟我一起去
I'll go talk to him. Miles, you wanna come with me?
好的  老大
Yeah, sure, boss.
好的  我需要你去找到Jack  Hurley和Kate
All right, I want you to find Jack and Hurley and Kate
越快越好  把他们弄到一起  看好
As quick as you can. put 'em in a house and sit on 'em.
-为什么  -因为我不想跟其他人说话
-What for?  -cause I don't want 'em talking to anybody else.
这里开始失去控制了
Things are starting to spin out of control here.
好的  我知道了
All right, I got it.
谁干的  知道是谁对我儿子干的么
Who did this? do you know who did this to my son?
现在我还不知道
Not yet
-我们正在查  他怎么样了  -我不知道
-But we're working on it. how's he doing?  -I don't know.
Juliet叫我在这里等
Juliet told me to wait out here.
-让我看看能不能给你带来点消息  -谢谢你了  Jim
-Let me see if I can get an update for ya. -Thanks, Jim.
你带着你的钥匙了么
You happen to have your keys with you?
是呀  怎么  你要干什么
Yeah. why? what do you need?
我可能忘在家里了
I must've left them at... at the house.
没关系  别担心
It's all right. don't worry about it.
纱布
More gauze.
-给  纱布  -好的  这里
-Here's some gauze. -Yeah, right here. yeah.
如果我们不能止住出血
If we can't stop the hemorrhaging,
要全都包扎起来  知道么
We're just gonna have to pack the whole tract. okay.
医生在哪
Where's the doctor?
在潜望镜站  星期五才回来
At the looking glass station till friday.
-怎么样  -不是很好  拉住
-How is he doing?  -Not well. hook him.
他的什么地方一直在出血  我解决不了
He's still bleeding in there somewhere, and I can't fix it.
没关系
It's all right.
不  有关系  这里需要人
No, it's not all right. someone needs to get in there
需要有人找到伤口并修复好
Who can find the damage that bullet did and fix it.
他需要一个真正的手术
He needs a real surgeon.
你是说我们被软禁了
You're telling us we're under house arrest?
不  你什么时候想离开都行
No, you're all free to leave whenever you want...
但我会向你的腿开枪
But I'll shoot you in the leg.
谁的主意
And whose idea was this?
你认为是谁
Who do you think?
Sawyer只是在做他的工作  Jack
Sawyer's just doing his job, Jack.
你在干什么  胖子
What the hell are you doing, tubby?
看我是不是消失了
Checking to see if I'm disappearing.
什么
What?
"回到未来"  伙计
"back to the future," man.
我们回到岛上的时间里
We came back in time to the island
还改变了一些事情  所以如果小Ben死了
And changed stuff. so if little Ben dies,
他永远不会长成大Ben
He'll never grow up to be big Ben,
成为那个一开始带我们回来的人
Who's one who made us come back here in the first place.
那就说明我们不在这里  就是说  伙计
Which means we can't be here. and therefore, dude?
我们不存在
We don't exist.
你是个笨蛋
You're an idiot.
我是吗
Am i?
不是像你说的那样
Yeah. it doesn't work like that.
你不能改变任何事情
You can't change anything.
你疯狂的伊拉克伙伴射击Linus
You're maniac Iraqi buddy shot Linus.
这是经常发生的事情  只是...
That is what always happened. it's just...
我们只是没有经历过
We never experienced how it all turns out.
令人困扰
This is really confusing.
我们已经习惯了
Yeah, well, get used to it.
但好消息是Linus没有死
But the good news is that linus didn't die,
所以那个孩子也不会死
So that means the kid can't either.
-他会好起来的  -那孩子看起来并不好
-He'll be fine.  -Didn't look like he was gonna be fine.
如果你错了会怎样
What if you're wrong?
如果我错了  我想我们会停止存在下去
Well, if I'm wrong, then I guess we all stop existing,
所有的事都无所谓了  对吗
And none of it matters anyway then, does it?
医生  需要你跟我来一下
Doc, I need you to come with me.
-跟你去哪  -Juliet说孩子在流血
-Come with you where?  -Juliet said the kid's losing blood
我们却没办法输给他任何东西
And we ain't got none to put back in him.
所以我们需要你找出来出血的地方
So we need you to show us where he sprung a leak.
不
No.
不  我不跟你去
No, I'm not coming with you.
如果你不来  Jack  那个孩子会死的
If you don't come with me, Jack, that kid's gonna die.
那就让他死吧
Then he dies.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
做点三明治
Making some sandwiches.
我想大家到现在都饿了
I figured everybody'd be getting hungry by now.
他只是个小男孩  Jack
He's just a boy, Jack.
你不能让他就这么死了
you can't just let him die.
你听到Miles的话了
You heard Miles.
我们改变不了任何已经发生的事情
we can't change what's already happened.
这不关我的事
This has nothing to do with me.
除非你是那个本该去救他的人
Unless you're the one who's supposed to save him.
三十年后  这个孩子会成为一个男人
30 years from now, that boy's gonna be a man
因为他需要手术而把我关起来
That locks me in a cage because he needs surgery.
然后你进来
And then you're gonna come in
求我去给他做手术
And you're gonna beg me to operate on him
因为他威胁到Sawyer
Because he's threateni to murder Sawyer.
我已经做过这种事情了
I've already done is once.
我已经救过一次Benjamin Linus
I've already saved Benjamin Linus
我是为你而做的  Kate
And I did it for you, Kate.
我不需要再做一次
I don't need to do it again.
这是我们的错误
This is our fault.
我们把Sayid带了回来  我们导致的这件事情
We brought Sayid back. we caused this.
你知道  我们来这之前
You know, when we were here before
我花了所有的时间去弥补一些事情
I spent all of my time trying to fix things.
但...你有没有想过
But... did you ever think
只是这个岛自己想去搞定
That maybe the island just wants to fix things itself?
而我可能
And maybe I was just...
在碍事
Gettin' in the way?
我不喜欢现在的你
You know, I don't like the new you.
我喜欢以前
I liked the old you,
那个不会坐以待毙的你
Who wouldn't just sit around and wait for things to happen.
你不喜欢以前的我  Kate
You didn't like the old me, Kate.
你去哪
Hey! Where are you going?
放松
Just relax.
你没事的
You're okay.
打扰一下  Juliet
I'm sorry. Juliet?
来了个新人
One of the new people is here.
她听说Ben需要输血  她说她是万能供血者
She heard Ben needed blood, says she's a universal donor.
可能会疼一下
This might hurt for a second.
很好 真勇敢
Good. Very brave.
James告诉我Jack不会帮忙
So James told me that Jack wouldn't help,
但他没说原因
But he didn't say why.
如果我知道Jack为什么做那些
If I understood why Jack does what he does,
我也一定不会待在这
I sure as hell wouldn't be sitting here.
离开岛后  你们俩有没有进展
Off island, did something happen with you two?
我们订婚了
We were engaged.
这算吗
Does that count?
-怎么回事  -Roger  我让你在外面等着
-What's going on?-Roger, I asked you to wait outside.
不  我的孩子怎么了
No, what's going on with my kid?
Kate在为我们提供血液
Kate is giving us some fresh blood
才能为Ben输血
So we can transfuse ben.
我不会就在外面等着
Well, I'm not waitin' outside.
他可以和我在一起  你去照顾Ben
You know, he could stay with me, and you could check on ben,
Roger陪着我
And...and Roger here could keep me company,
确保我不会昏倒
Make sure I don't pass out.
好吧  Roger  坐下吧
Okay. roger, have a seat.
-谢谢  -应该的
-Thanks. -Sure.
他偷了我的钥匙
He stole my keys.
什么
Sorry?
Lafluer问我  我的钥匙在哪里
Lafleur asked me where my keys were.
那杂种没问其他问题 他不知道答案
That bastard doesn't ask any questions He doesn't know the answers to...
这意味着我儿子偷了钥匙
Which means my son stole my keys
他放走了那个混蛋
So he could bust that animal out of jail.
他为什么这么做
Why...why would he do that?
因为我
Because of me.
你有孩子吗
You got kids?
没
No.
我曾以为我可以是最棒的父亲
I thought I was gonna be the greatest father ever.
你知道吗
You know?
我想这没实现
I guess it didn't work out that way.
他妈妈呢  她还在这吗
What about his mother? Is she still around?
不  死了
No, she's dead.
她在分娩那天就死了
She died the day he was born.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我一直都很努力
I tried to do
去做我认为她希望我去做的事
What I thought she'd want me to do,
但
But...
我想一个男孩子还是需要母亲的
I guess a boy just needs his mother.
-怎么了  -他缺氧性休克了
-What's going on?-He's going into hypoxic shock.
什么意思  他怎么了
What does that mean?What's the matter with him?!
他需要更多的氧气
He needs more oxygen.
Roger出去
Roger, get out of here!
-什么  -把他弄出去
-What?-Get him out of here!
等等  怎么了  等等
Wait! what...what is... wait a minute.
Roger请在外面等着
Please, roger, just wait outside.
我们直说
Let me get this straight.
这些都是已经发生的事了
All this already happened.
是的
Yes.
所以现在我们的谈话
So this conversation we're having right now...
已经发生过了
We already had it.
是的
Yes!
-那我下面该说什么  -我不知道
-Then what am I gonna say next?-I don't know.
那么你的理论就错了
Ha! Then your theory is wrong!
说了千遍了
For the thousandth time, you dingbat,
我们的谈话已经发生过了
The conversation already happened,
但不是对我们俩而言
But not for you and me.
对我们俩而言  现在才发生
For you and me, it's happening right now.
好吧  回答我
Okay, answer me this.
如果这些对我都发生过了
If all this already happened to me,
那么  为什么我什么都不记得了
Then... Why don't I remember any of it?
因为Ben曾经转过那轮子
Because once Ben turned that wheel,
对我们来说
Time isn't a straight line
时间不是直线型的
For us anymore.
我们过去的经历在未来
Our experiences in the past
而未来
And the future
在现在以前发生
Occurred before these experiences right now.
再说一遍
Say that again.
用枪杀了我吧  拜托了
Shoot me. please. please?
我不能杀了你
Aha! I can't shoot you.
因为如果你在1977死了的话
Because if you die in 1977,
那你就不能在30年后坐船
Then you'll never come back to the island on the freighter
-去岛上  -我能死
-30 years from now.-I can die
因为我已经坐船去了岛上
Because I've already come to the island on the freighter.
我们中的任何人都可以死
Any of us can die
因为这是我们的现在
because this is our present.
但你说Ben不会死  因为他还要长大
But you said Ben couldn't die because he still has to grow up
成为小岛居民的首领  因为这才是他的过去
And become the leader of the others. Because this is his past.
但是当我们抓住Ben  Sayid折磨他
But when we first captured ben, and sayid, like, tortured him,
那么他为什么不记得
Then why wouldn't he remember
当他是孩子时  被同一人射中
Getting shot by that same guy when he was a kid?
我没想过这个
I hadn't thought of that.
他怎么样了
How is he?
-他稳定下来了  -他不会有事吧
-He's stable.-Is he gonna be okay?
他输过血了
He's got some fresh blood running through him,
这是好事
Which is a good thing.
Roger  你要去医疗救护站
Roger, I need you to go out to the medical station.
他们那里有  我们没有的设备
There are some supplies there that we don't have here.
好的  我想说  我想说谢谢
Okay. hey, I just wanna say, i-i... I wanna say thanks.
我知道你尽力
I know that you're doing everything you can...
去救他
To save him, and...
好的  我这就去  好吧
All right, I'm...i'm gonna go, okay?
他好点了没
Is he any better?
他情况稳定了
He is stable now.
但我不能
But I can't, um...
我治不好
I can't fix it.
潜艇呢  我是说  能不能把他带走
What about the sub? I mean, can we take him somewhere?
不  它离开了  几个月内它不会回来的
No. it's gone.It won't be back for a couple of months.
但他不会死
But he can't die, right?
他会死的
He is going to die.
他在一个没有条件的救护站里
He is in a medical situation that is not resolvable.
好的  我们不能无所事事
Okay, well, we can't just sit here and do nothing.
一定有人能帮助他
I mean, there's got to be someone who can help him.
我们有整个
We have entire...
什么
What?
或许他们可以做些什么
Maybe there's something they can do.
他们
"they"?
"其他人"
The others.
你抱好他了吗
You got him?
是的  准备好了吗  好的  1  2  3   走
Yeah. ready? okay. all right. one, two, three, go.
好的  我们走
Okay, let's go.
我跟你一起去  不  如果出了事
I'm coming with you. no, no, no, no. if something goes wrong
或者我们被抓  我无所谓
Or we get caught, it doesn't matter for me,
你的生活就不复存在了
But you've got a whole life here.
而且如果Sawyer知道我让你卷入了这些
And besides, if sawyer knew that I got you involved in this,
他饶不了我  你打算怎么办
He'd kill me. how are you gonna manage?
我会处理的  别担心
I'll manag don't worry.
Kate  Sawyer会发现Ben不见的
Kate, sawyer's gonna find out ben's gone,
如果他发现了  我不得不告诉他发生了什么
And when he does, I have to tell him what happened.
不过我会尽量为你拖延时间
But I'll give you as much of a head start as I can.
祝你好运
Good luck.
有个人
There's someone...
在洛杉矶
Someone here in los angeles.
我带你去见他们  谁
Let me take you to them. who?
就是要向我们展示
The same person that's gonna show us
如何回岛上的人
How to get back the island.
原来是这么回事
Is that what this is about?
你知道这件事  不  我
You knew about this. no. no, I was o...
你就是因为这个假装关心Aaron
And that is why you were pretending to care about aaron,
说服我回到那  我没假装做任何事
To convince me to go back there?! I wasn't pretending anything.
这太疯狂了  你们都疯了  Kate
This is insane. you guys are crazy. kate...
Jack  别说了
Jack, don't!
妈妈  我渴了
Mommy, I'm thirsty.
我想喝牛奶
I need some milk.
请在第2款台结账
Price check on 2. price check on 2.
你要巧克力牛奶还是纯牛奶
Do you want chocolate milk or regular milk?
果汁
Juice box.
你不喝牛奶了
You don't want milk anymore?
果汁
Juice box.
请问果汁在哪
Excuse me. where are you juice boxes?
谢谢
Thank you very much.
请不要在第3款台排队等待
No waiting on check stand 3. no waiting on check stand 3.
Aaron
Aaron?
请问你看到我儿子了吗
Um, excuse me. have you seen my son?
什么
I'm sorry?
3岁  金发
A little 3-year-old blond?
Aaron
Aaron?
Aaron?!
我儿子丢了  三岁  金发男孩
I've lost my son. he's 3. he's a little blond boy.
别担心  夫人  我马上发个公告
Don't worry, ma'am. I'll make an announcement.
不  你要马上封锁这里  你
No, no, no. you have to seal off the store. you...
Aaron
Aaron?
这是你的妈妈吗  亲爱的  这是你妈妈吗
Hey! hey, is this your mommy? honey, is this your mommy?
我在水果摊那里发现了他
I found him in the fruit section.
他好像是迷路了  我正要发公告
I...he looked lost. I was getting ready to make an announcement.
谢谢你  谢谢
Thank you. thank you very much.
好了  亲爱的  妈妈找到你了
It's okay, honey. mommy's got you.
妈妈找到你了
Mommy's got you.
告诉
Tell...
告诉我...  别说了行吗
Tell my... try not to talk, okay?
告诉我爸我很抱歉偷了他的钥匙
Tell my dad I'm sorry I stole his keys.
我知道你想阻止我
I know you gotta stop me...
可是我不能就这样这孩子去死
But I can't just let that kid die.
雀斑女  我不是来阻止你的
Damn it, freckles. I ain't here to stop you.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
Kate阿姨
Hi, auntie kate!
Clementine  你妈妈在家吗
Hi, clementine. is your mommy home?
是的  我去叫她  好的
Sure. I'll go get her. okay.
他们要回去  回到岛上去
They're going back? to the island?
上帝啊  他们为什么要回去
Why in god's name would they wanna do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
Jack说我们不应该离开那
Jack says that we weren't supposed to leave.
Jack好像是个有道理的人
Well, jack sounds like a piece of work.
你看起来很累
You look exhausted.
喝了这个  去我床上休息一下吧
Drink this. curl up on my bed. take a nap.
我会照顾你儿子
I'll watch your fella.
我把他弄丢了
I lost him.
什么
What?
我不知道发生了什么  我们在超市
I don't know what happened. we were in the supermarket,
我就回了一下头  他就不见了
And I turned around for one second, and he was gone.
最疯狂的是
And, you know, the crazy thing is, is that...
我很害怕
As scared as I was...
可是我一点都不惊讶
I wasn't surprised.
我想也是时候了
All I could think was, it's about time.
为什么我会这样想
Why would I feel that way?
为什么我就想到他有可能是被带走了
I mean, why would I expect him to be taken?
因为你带走了他  Kate
Because you took him, kate.
不  我...
No, i...
Claire走了
Claire was gone.
她离开了他
I mean, she left him.
我不得不照顾他  他需要我
I had to take him. he needed me.
你需要他
You needed him.
Sawyer伤了你的心
Sawyer broke your heart.
你该怎么抚慰你的心
How else were you supposed to fix it?
想想办法
Figure out
你该怎么把他带出这里
How you re gonna carry him out there by yourself?
防线就在右边  对吗
Well, the line's just right over there, right?
其他人在另一边
The others are on the other side.
他们没在那
well, they ain't right on the other side.
我们该走了
We better get movin'. hey.
为什么帮我
Why are you doing this? why are you helping me?
当我发现Ben不见了
When I found out ben was gone,
Juliet告诉我你带走了他
And juliet told me what you were up to,
我也问这个问题
I asked that exact damn question...
你为什么帮Ben
Why are you helping ben?
她说
And she said...
不管这孩子长大时什么样
No matter what he's gonna grow up to be,
都不应该让他死
It's wrong to let a kid die.
所以...
So...
这就是我这么做的原因
That's why I'm doing this.
我为她做这些的
I'm doing it for her.
Jack在哪
Where's jack?
我想他在洗澡
Uhhe...he's in the shower. I think.
找他有事吗  我有事要跟他说
Is he in trouble? I just need to talk to him.
让我们单独谈谈好吗
You two mind giving us some privacy?
多问我点时间旅行的问题
Hey, ask me more questions about time travel.
我需要你
I needed you.
什么
I'm sorry?
那个孩子失血过多  你是外科医生
That kid was bleeding out. you're a surgeon,
我需要你帮忙  那孩子是Ben
And I needed you. that kid is ben.
还不是Ben  他只是个孩子
That's not ben yet. he's just a kid.
Juliet  对不起  我不能帮你
Juliet, I'm sorry. I can't help you.
我不是请你帮忙  Jack
I'm not asking for your help, jack.
你很明显不感兴趣
You made it pretty clear you weren't interested.
Sawyer和Kate正在帮他
It's up to sawyer and kate now.
什么  她正在试着救他
What? she's trying to save him,
我让James去帮她
And I sent james after her to help
因为他们真的关心他
Because they actually care.
我回来是因为我在意  Juliet
I came back here because I care, juliet.
为了救你们我才回来的
I came back here because I was trying to save you.
我们不需要你救
We didn't need saving!
这三年来我们过的很好
We've been fine for three years.
你是为你自己回来的
You came back here for you.
至少行行好告诉我为什么
At least do me the courtesy of telling me why.
我回来
I came back...
因为这是应该的
Because I was supposed to.
应该干什么
Supposed to do what?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
那你最好搞清楚
Well, you'd better figure it out.
你知道  我可以抱着他
You know, I can take him for a while.
你当然可以
Sure you can.
你知道么他爸爸说你认为是Ben放Sayid出去的
You know,his father said that you think ben broke sayid out.
小孩么  什么事情都可能做
Kid'll do almost anything
如果他被惹怒了的话
If he's pissed off enough at his folks.
这就是为什么你要我照顾你女儿
Is that why you asked me to take care of your daughter?
你去了么
Did you?
当然了
Of course I did.
来  把他的头向后倾
Go ahead and tip his head back.
她长的什么样
What's she like?
Clementine
Clementine?
对  Clementine
Yeah. clementine.
她很漂亮
Oh, she's beautiful.
她笑起来和你一模一样
Looks just like you when she smiles.
她长的很快
She's growing up fast.
已经有自己的态度了
Already has a little attitude.
你和Cassidy有很多话说
I bet you and cassidy had a lot to talk about.
她有着自己有趣的理论
She had an interesting theory
关于你跳出直升机的理由
On why you jumped off the chopper.
是么  是怎样地
Yeah? what's that?
她认为你是担心
She thought you were worried
如果你没有会怎样
About what would happen if you didn't.
你和我没有可能Kate
You and me would've never worked out, kate.
我一点都不适合当你男友
I wasn't any more fit to be your boyfriend
而且我要当那个小女孩的父亲
Than I am to be that little girl's father.
看起来你和Juliet不错
You seem to be doing all right with juliet.
是
Yeah.
这三年我成熟不少
I've done a lot of growing up the past three years.
不许动
Do not move.
我说不许动
I said don't move.
这是违反了休战条例
this is a violation of the truce.
-你过界了  -我们知道
-You're over the line. -We know.
这孩子中枪了  这是我们双方的问题
This kid's been shot. That's both of our problems.
除非你想要战争
So unless you want to go to war,
否则就带我们去找Richard Alpert
You're gonna take us to Richard Alpert,
现在就去
And you're gonna do it now.
Littleton女士
Mrs. Littleton,
我是Kate Austen
Um, I'm Kate Austen.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
请进
Come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
你朋友Shephard医生昨晚来过
Your friend dr. Shephard came here last night,
不停地说一个叫Aaron人
Going on and on about some person name Aaron.
我问他那是谁
When I asked him who that was,
他撒腿就跑
He ran out of here like the room was on fire.
他是你的孙子
He's your grandson.
你女儿Claire
And your daughter Claire...
还活着
Is alive.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
Claire死于那次飞机事故
Claire died in the plane crash.
不  她活下来了
No, she survived.
当飞机失事时  你女儿怀孕8个月了
When we crashed, your daughter was eight months pregnant,
她是唯一在那个岛上分娩的人  而不是我
And... she's the one who gave birth on the island, not me.
我们说了谎
We lied.
那儿有其他幸存者  我们抛弃了他们
There were other survivors, too. We just left them behind.
为什么
Why?
为什么你们抛弃了她
Why would you leave her there?
因为她失踪了
Because she disappeared,
她丢下了孩子  我们四处寻找
And she left the baby behind. we looked everywhere, but...
我开始照顾Aaron
That's when I started taking care of Aaron.
当我们获救  我们没有
And when we were rescued, we didn't...
我们要决定该对他怎么办
We had to decide what to do with him.
我知道她希望他被收养
And I knew that she had wanted him to be adopted,
但我做不到
But I couldn't
我想要保护他
I had to protect him,
所以我说他是我的孩子
So I said he was mine.
你为什么要说谎
Why did you lie?
为什么你没有先来找我
Why didn't you come to me in the first place?
因为我需要他
Because I needed him.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你会看见他非常的可爱
You're gonna see that he's so sweet
善良又优秀
And kind and good.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我住在你两层楼下
Um, I checked in two doors down.
他睡着了
He's asleep.
我知道你要承受很多
I know that this is a lot for you to handle.
但是
But...
等你准备好了
When you're ready,
他在等你
He's waiting for you.
我告诉他  你是他的奶奶
I told him that you're his grandmother,
我走了以后你来照顾他
That you'll take care of him while I'm gone
我很快就回来
And that I'll be back soon.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我回去找你的女儿
I'm going back to find your daughter.
再见  宝贝儿
Bye-bye, baby.
别担心  他们就在那等着我们
Don't worry. we got 'em right where we want 'em.
-闭嘴  快走  -我看起来在干嘛
-Shut up and keep movin -What's it look like I'm doing?
好啊  James
Hello there, James.
你到底从哪冒出来的
Where the hell did you come from?
你让我的人带你来找我  你找到了
You asked my people to bring you to me. here I am.
那是Benjamin Linus吗
Is that Benjamin Linus?
你们认识吗
You two know each other?
他怎么了
What happened to him?
他中枪了
He was shot.
-你是谁  -她跟我在一起
-And who might you be?-She's with me.
你们为什么来这
And why are you here?
因为我们要你去救他  可以吗
'cause we need you to save his life. Can you?
如果我救了他  他就会改变的
If I take him, he's not ever gonna be the same again.
什么意思
What do you mean by that?
我是说
What I mean is that...
他会忘了所发生的一切
He'll forget this ever happened, and that...
他不会再那么天真
His innocence will be gone.
他永远是我们的一员
He will always be one of us.
你还是想让我带他走吗
You still want me to take him?
是的
Yes.
Richard
Richard...
你应该问问Ellie
You shouldn't do this without asking Ellie.
如果Charles发现了  那就随他去
And if Charles finds out... Let him find out.
我不会回答他们的
I don't answer to either of them.
你要带他去哪
Wh-where are you taking him?
别跟着了
Come on.
你好  Ben
Hello, Ben.
欢迎回到人间
Welcome back to the land of the living.